Finding Aid for the William and Lee Bell Scripts for Television Soap Operas PASC.0096
UCLA Library Special Collections
- YOUNG AND THE RESTLESS, THE
  - Prod. #3882-3888. Aired: 06/29/88-07/06/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 438)
  - Prod. #3889-3895. Aired: 07/07/88-07/15/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 439)
  - Prod. #3896-3902. Aired: 07/07/88-07/26/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 440)
  - Prod. #3913-3917. Aired: 08/10/88-08/16/88. Notes: SCRIPTS, OUTLINES, AND TIMING SCRIPTS. (Box 443)
  - Prod. #3923-3924. Aired: 08/24/88-08/25/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 445)
  - Prod. #3926-3930. Aired: 08/29/88-09/02/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 445)
  - Prod. #3931-3937. Aired: 09/06/88-09/15/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 446)
  - Prod. #3938-3944. Aired: 09/16/88-09/26/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 447)
  - Prod. #3945-3951. Aired: 09/27/88-10/05/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 3948). (Box 448)
  - Prod. #3952-3958. Aired: 10/06/88-10/14/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 449)
  - Prod. #3959-3965. Aired: 10/17/88-10/25/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 3961). (Box 450)
  - Prod. #3966-3973. Aired: 10/26/88-11/04/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO SCRIPT FOR 3966). (Box 451)
  - Prod. #3974-3981. Aired: 11/05/88-11/16/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINES FOR 3974, 78, 81). (Box 452)
  - Prod. #3982-3988. Aired: 11/17/88-11/29/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 453)
  - Prod. #3989-3995. Aired: 11/30/88-12/08/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 3991). (Box 454)
  - Prod. #3996-4002. Aired: 12/09/88-12/19/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4002). (Box 455)
  - Prod. #4003-4009. Aired: 12/20/88-12/29/88. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4007). (Box 456)
  - Prod. #4010-4016. Aired: 12/30/88-01/10/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 457)
  - Prod. #4017-4023. Aired: 01/11/89-01/19/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 458)
  - Prod. #4024-4030. Aired: 01/23/89-01/31/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 459)
  - Prod. #4031-4037. Aired: 02/01/89-02/09/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 460)
  - Prod. #4038-4044. Aired: 02/10/89-02/21/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 461)
  - Prod. #4045-4051. Aired: 02/22/89-03/02/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 462)
  - Prod. #4052-4058. Aired: 03/03/89-03/13/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4054). (Box 463)
  - Prod. #4059-4065. Aired: 03/14/89-03/22/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 464)
  - Prod. #4066-4072. Aired: 03/23/89-03/31/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 465)
  - Prod. #4073-4079. Aired: 04/03/89-04/11/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 466)
  - Prod. #4080-4086. Aired: 04/12/89-04/20/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 467)
  - Prod. #4087-4093. Aired: 04/21/89-05/01/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 468)
  - Prod. #4094-4100. Aired: 05/02/89-05/10/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 469)
  - Prod. #4101-4107. Aired: 05/11/89-05/19/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 470)
  - Prod. #4108-4114. Aired: 05/22/89-05/30/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 471)
  - Prod. #4115-4121. Aired: 05/31/89-06/08/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 472)
  - Prod. #4122-4128. Aired: 06/09/89-06/19/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 473)
  - Prod. #4129-4135. Aired: 06/20/89-06/28/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 474)
  - Prod. #4136-4142. Aired: 06/29/89-07/07/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 475)
  - Prod. #4143-4149. Aired: 07/10/89-07/18/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4149). (Box 476)
  - Prod. #4150-4156. Aired: 07/19/89-07/27/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 477)
  - Prod. #4157-4164. Aired: 07/28/89-08/08/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 478)
  - Prod. #4165-4171. Aired: 08/09/89-08/17/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 479)
  - Prod. #4172-4179. Aired: 08/18/89-08/29/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO SCRIPT FOR 4174). (Box 480)
  - Prod. #4180-4186. Aired: 08/30/89-09/11/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 481)
  - Prod. #4187-4193. Aired: 09/12/89-09/20/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 482)
  - Prod. #4194-4201. Aired: 09/21/89-10/02/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO SCRIPT FOR 4200). (Box 483)
  - Prod. #4202-4208. Aired: 10/03/89-10/11/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 484)
  - Prod. #4209-4216. Aired: 10/12/89-10/23/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4212). (Box 485)
  - Prod. #4217-4223. Aired: 10/24/89-11/01/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 486)
  - Prod. #4224-4230. Aired: 11/02/89-11/10/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 487)
  - Prod. #4231-4238. Aired: 11/13/89-11/22/89. Notes: SCRIPTS & OUTLINES (NO OL FOR 4231, 37) (NO SCRIPT FOR 4238). (Box 488)
  - Prod. #4239-4246. Aired: 11/27/89-12/06/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 489)
  - Prod. #4247-4253. Aired: 12/07/89-12/15/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 490)
  - Prod. #4254-4260. Aired: 12/18/89-12/27/89. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 491)
  - Prod. #4261-4267. Aired: 12/28/89-01/08/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 492)
  - Prod. #4268-4274. Aired: 01/09/90-01/17/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 493)
  - Prod. #4275-4282. Aired: 01/18/90-01/29/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OL FOR 4277) (NO SCRIPT FOR 4279). (Box 494)
  - Prod. #4283-4289. Aired: 01/30/90-02/07/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 495)
  - Prod. #4290-4297. Aired: 02/08/90-02/19/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO SCRIPT FOR 4291). (Box 496)
  - Prod. #4298. Aired: 02/20/90. Notes: SCRIPT AND OUTLINE. (Box 497)
  - Prod. #4346-4352. Aired: 04/27/90-05/07/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO SCRIPT FOR 4350). (Box 497)
  - Prod. #4353-4359. Aired: 05/08/90-05/16/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 498)
  - Prod. #4360-4366. Aired: 05/17/90-05/25/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4366). (Box 499)
  - Prod. #4367-4374. Aired: 05/28/90-06/06/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 500)
  - Prod. #4375-4382. Aired: 06/07/90-06/18/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4381). (Box 501)
  - Prod. #4383-4389. Aired: 06/19/90-06/27/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4383). (Box 502)
  - Prod. #4390-4397. Aired: 06/28/90-07/09/90. Notes: SCRIPTS & OUTLINES (NO SCRIPT FOR 4393)(NO OUTLINE FOR 4394). (Box 503)
  - Prod. #4398-4404. Aired: 07/10/90-07/18/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 504)
  - Prod. #4405-4411. Aired: 07/19/90-07/27/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 505)
  - Prod. #4412-4421. Aired: 07/30/90-08/10/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO SCRIPTS FOR 4413, 15, 18). (Box 506)
  - Prod. #4422-4428. Aired: 08/13/90-08/21/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 507)
  - Prod. #4429-4435. Aired: 08/22/90-08/30/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 508)
  - Prod. #4436-4442. Aired: 08/31/90-09/12/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 509)
  - Prod. #4443-4449. Aired: 09/13/90-09/21/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 510)
  - Prod. #4450-4456. Aired: 09/24/90-10/02/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 511)
  - Prod. #4457-4463. Aired: 10/03/90-10/11/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 512)
  - Prod. #4464-4471. Aired: 10/12/90-10/23/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINES FOR 4464, 66, 68). (Box 513)
  - Prod. #4472-4479. Aired: 10/24/90-11/02/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4478). (Box 514)
  - Prod. #4480-4487. Aired: 11/05/90-11/14/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINES FOR 4480, 83, 84). (Box 515)
  - Prod. #4488-4489. Aired: 11/15/90-11/16/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 516)
  - Prod. #4491-4496. Aired: 11/20/90-11/29/90. Notes: SCRIPTS & OUTLINES (NO SCRIPT FOR 4491) (NO OL FOR 4494, 95). (Box 516)
  - Prod. #4497-4504. Aired: 11/30/90-12/11/90. Notes: SCRIPTS & OUTLINES (NO SCRIPT FOR 4500) (NO OL FOR 4501, 02). (Box 517)
  - Prod. #4505-4511. Aired: 12/12/90-12/20/90. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4506). (Box 518)
  - Prod. #4512-4518. Aired: 12/21/90-01/02/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 519)
  - Prod. #4519. Aired: 01/03/91. Notes: OUTLINE ONLY. (Box 520)
  - Prod. #4546-4552. Aired: 02/11/91-02/20/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4549). (Box 520)
  - Prod. #4553-4559. Aired: 02/21/91-03/01/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 521)
  - Prod. #4560-4567. Aired: 03/04/91-03/13/91. Notes: SCRIPTS & OUTLINES (NO SCRIPT FOR 4562) (NO OL FOR 4560). (Box 522)
  - Prod. #4568-4574. Aired: 03/18/91-03/26/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 523)
  - Prod. #4575-4581. Aired: 03/27/91-04/04/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 524)
  - Prod. #4582-4589. Aired: 04/05/91-04/16/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO SCRIPT FOR 4582). (Box 525)
  - Prod. #4590-4597. Aired: 04/17/91-04/26/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO SCRIPT FOR 4591). (Box 526)
  - Prod. #4598-4604. Aired: 04/29/91-05/07/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 527)
  - Prod. #4605. Aired: 05/08/91. Notes: SCRIPT AND OUTLINE. (Box 528)
  - Prod. #4607-4612. Aired: 05/10/91-05/17/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 528)
  - Prod. #4613-4620. Aired: 05/20/91-05/29/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINES FOR 4614, 18). (Box 529)
  - Prod. #4621-4627. Aired: 05/30/91-06/07/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 530)
  - Prod. #4628-4634. Aired: 06/10/91-06/18/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4631). (Box 531)
  - Prod. #4635-4641. Aired: 06/19/91-06/27/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 532)
  - Prod. #4642-4649. Aired: 06/28/91-07/09/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINES FOR 4642, 44, 46). (Box 533)
  - Prod. #4650-4656. Aired: 07/10/91-07/18/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 534)
  - Prod. #4657-4663. Aired: 07/19/91-07/29/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 535)
  - Prod. #4664-4671. Aired: 07/30/91-08/08/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINES FOR 4666, 69). (Box 536)
  - Prod. #4672-4678. Aired: 08/09/91-08/19/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 537)
  - Prod. #4679-4685. Aired: 08/20/91-08/28/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 538)
  - Prod. #4686-4692. Aired: 08/29/91-09/10/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 539)
  - Prod. #4693-4699. Aired: 09/11/91-09/19/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 540)
  - Prod. #4700-4706. Aired: 09/20/91-10/01/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 541)
  - Prod. #4707-4713. Aired: 10/02/91-10/10/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINES FOR 4707, 08, 12). (Box 542)
  - Prod. #4714-4720. Aired: 10/11/91-10/21/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 543)
  - Prod. #4721-4727. Aired: 10/22/91-10/30/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 544)
  - Prod. #4728-4734. Aired: 10/31/91-11/08/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 545)
  - Prod. #4735-4742. Aired: 11/11/91-11/21/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINES FOR 4735, 36, 42). (Box 546)
  - Prod. #4743-4749. Aired: 11/22/91-12/03/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 547)
  - Prod. #4750-4756. Aired: 12/04/91-12/12/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4750). (Box 548)
  - Prod. #4757-4763. Aired: 12/13/91-12/23/91. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4757). (Box 549)
  - Prod. #4764-4770. Aired: 12/24/91-01/03/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 550)
  - Prod. #4771-4777. Aired: 01/06/92-01/14/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4771). (Box 551)
  - Prod. #4778-4784. Aired: 01/15/92-01/23/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4781). (Box 552)
  - Prod. #4785-4791. Aired: 01/24/92-02/03/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4786). (Box 553)
  - Prod. #4792-4798. Aired: 02/04/92-02/12/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 554)
  - Prod. #4799-4805. Aired: 02/13/92-02/24/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 555)
  - Prod. #4806-4812. Aired: 02/25/92-03/04/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 556)
  - Prod. #4813-4819. Aired: 03/05/92-03/13/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 557)
  - Prod. #4820-4827. Aired: 03/16/92-03/30/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINES FOR 4823, 25). (Box 558)
  - Prod. #4828-4835. Aired: 03/31/92-04/09/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINES FOR 4832, 33). (Box 559)
  - Prod. #4836-4843. Aired: 04/10/92-04/21/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO SCRIPT FOR 4841) (NO OL FOR 4842). (Box 560)
  - Prod. #4844-4850. Aired: 04/22/92-04/30/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 561)
  - Prod. #4851-4857. Aired: 05/01/92-05/11/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 562)
  - Prod. #4858-4864. Aired: 05/12/92-05/20/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 563)
  - Prod. #4865-4872. Aired: 05/21/92-06/01/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO SCRIPTS FOR 4869, 71). (Box 564)
  - Prod. #4873-4879. Aired: 06/02/92-06/10/92. Notes: SCRIPTS & OUTLINES INC. TIMING SCRIPT FOR 4876 (NO OL 4873). (Box 565)
  - Prod. #4880-4886. Aired: 06/11/92-06/19/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 566)
  - Prod. #4887-4893. Aired: 06/22/92-06/30/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 567)
  - Prod. #4894-4900. Aired: 07/01/92-07/09/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4898). (Box 568)
  - Prod. #4901-4906. Aired: 07/10/92-07/17/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 569)
  - Prod. #4907-4913. Aired: 07/20/92-07/28/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 570)
  - Prod. #4914-4920. Aired: 07/29/92-08/06/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 571)
  - Prod. #4921-4927. Aired: 08/07/92-08/17/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 572)
  - Prod. #4928-4935. Aired: 08/18/92-08/27/92. Notes: SCRIPTS & OUTLINES (NO SCRIPT FOR 4931) (NO OL FOR 4929). (Box 573)
  - Prod. #4936-4942. Aired: 08/28/92-09/08/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 574)
  - Prod. #4943-4949. Aired: 09/09/92-09/18/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 575)
  - Prod. #4950-4956. Aired: 09/21/92-09/29/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 576)
  - Prod. #4957-4963. Aired: 09/30/92-10/08/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 577)
  - Prod. #4964-4970. Aired: 10/09/92-10/19/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4969). (Box 578)
  - Prod. #4971-4974. Aired: 10/20/92-10/23/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OUTLINE FOR 4972). (Box 579)
  - Aired:. Notes: CAST HEADSHOTS & BIOS, CASTLIST, FACTSHEET, PRESS RELEASES, AWARDS WON, ARTICLES FROM TRADES (12/92). (Box 580)
  - Prod. #4975-4982. Aired: 10/26/92-11/04/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 581)
  - Prod. #4983-4990. Aired: 11/05/92-11/16/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 582)
  - Prod. #4991-4998. Aired: 11/17/92-11/28/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 583)
  - Prod. #4999-5006. Aired: 11/30/92-12/09/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OL FOR 5004). (Box 584)
  - Prod. #5007-5014. Aired: 12/10/92-12/21/92. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OL FOR 5009). (Box 585)
  - Prod. #5015-5022. Aired: 12/22/92-01/04/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 586)
  - Prod. #5023-5030. Aired: 01/05/93-01/14/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OL FOR 5027, 5029). (Box 587)
  - Prod. #5031-5039. Aired: 01/15/93-01/28/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OL FOR 5038). (Box 588)
  - Prod. #5040-5047. Aired: 01/29/93-02/09/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 589)
  - Prod. #5048-5055. Aired: 02/10/93-02/19/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 590)
  - Prod. #5056-5063. Aired: 02/22/93-03/03/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 591)
  - Prod. #5064-5070. Aired: 03/04/93-03/12/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 592)
  - Prod. #5071-5078. Aired: 03/15/93-03/26/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 593)
  - Prod. #5079-5086. Aired: 03/29/93-04/07/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 594)
  - Prod. #5087-5094. Aired: 04/08/93-04/19/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 595)
  - Prod. #5095-5102. Aired: 04/20/93-04/29/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OL FOR 5095). (Box 596)
  - Prod. #5103-5111. Aired: 04/30/93-05/12/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OL FOR 5108) (NO SCRIPT FOR 5104). (Box 597)
  - Prod. #5112-5117. Aired: 05/13/93-05/20/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (NO OL FOR 5113, 5116). (Box 598)
  - Prod. #5118-5126. Aired: 05/21/93-06/02/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES, NO OL FOR 5119 & 5125, NO SCRIPT FOR 5126. (Box 610)
  - Prod. #5127-5134. Aired: 06/03/93-06/14/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 611)
  - Prod. #5135-5142. Aired: 06/15/93-06/24/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 612)
  - Prod. #5143-5150. Aired: 06/25/93-07/06/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (no outline #5148, 5150). (Box 613)
  - Prod. #5151-5157. Aired: 07/07/93-07/15/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 614)
  - Prod. #5158-5164. Aired: 07/16/93-07/26/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 615)
  - Prod. #5165-5171. Aired: 07/27/93-08/04/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 616)
  - Prod. #5172-5178. Aired: 08/05/93-08/13/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 617)
  - Prod. #5179-5185. Aired: 08/16/93-08/24/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES, NO OL FOR 5184. (Box 618)
  - Prod. #5186-5192. Aired: 08/25/93-09/02/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 619)
  - Prod. #5193-5200. Aired: 09/03/93-09/16/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 620)
  - Prod. #5201-5208. Aired: 09/17/93-09/28/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 621)
  - Prod. #5209-5214. Aired: 09/29/93-10/06/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 622)
  - Prod. #5215-5221. Aired: 10/07/93-10/15/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 623)
  - Prod. #5222-5228. Aired: 10/18/93-10/26/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 624)
  - Prod. #5229-5236. Aired: 10/27/93-11/05/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES, NO OL FOR 5231. (Box 625)
  - Prod. #5237-5243. Aired: 11/08/93-11/16/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 626)
  - Prod. #5244-5251. Aired: 11/17/93-11/29/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (no outline # 5240). (Box 627)
  - Prod. #5252-5259. Aired: 11/30/93-12/09/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES, (no script # 5256). (Box 628)
  - Prod. #5260-5266. Aired: 12/10/93-12/20/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 629)
  - Prod. #5267-5274. Aired: 12/21/93-12/30/93. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES (no script # 5272). (Box 630)
  - Prod. #5275-5282. Aired: 12/31/93-01/11/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 631)
  - Prod. #5283-5284. Aired: 01/12/94-01/13/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 632)
  - Prod. #5444-5447. Aired: 09/12/94-09/15/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 653)
  - Prod. #5448-5453. Aired: 09/16/94-09/26/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 654)
  - Prod. #5454-5459. Aired: 09/27/94-10/04/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 655)
  - Prod. #5460-5471. Aired: 10/05/94-10/12/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 656)
  - Prod. #5472-5477. Aired: 10/21/94-10/28/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 658)
  - Prod. #5478-5484. Aired: 11/01/94-11/08/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 659)
  - Prod. #5334-5336. Aired: 03/29/94-03/31/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 660)
  - Prod. #5485-5488. Aired: 11/09/94-11/14/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 660)
  - Prod. #5337-5343. Aired: 04/01/94-04/11/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 661)
  - Prod. #5344-5350. Aired: 04/12/94-04/20/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 662)
  - Prod. #5351-5355. Aired: 04/21/94-04/27/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 663)
  - Prod. #5285. Aired: 01/14/94. Notes: SCRIPT AND OUTLINE. (Box 668)
  - Prod. #5286-5292. Aired: 01/17/94-01/25/94. Notes: OUTLINES AND SCRIPTS. (Box 669)
  - Prod. #5293-5299. Aired: 01/26/94-02/03/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 670)
  - Prod. #5300-5306. Aired: 02/04/94-02/14/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 671)
  - Prod. #5307-5309. Aired: 02/16/94-02/18/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 672)
  - Prod. #5395-5397. Aired: 06/22/94-06/24/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 672)
  - Prod. #5398-5407. Aired: 06/27/94-07/08/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 673)
  - Prod. #5408-5415. Aired: 07/11/94-07/20/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 674)
  - Prod. #5416-5421. Aired: 07/21/94-07/28/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 675)
  - Prod. #5381-5387. Aired: 06/02/94-06/10/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 676)
  - Prod. #5356-5357. Aired: 04/28/94-04/29/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 677)
  - Prod. #5388-5394. Aired: 06/13/94-06/21/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 677)
  - Prod. #5358-5364. Aired: 05/02/94-05/10/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 678)
  - Prod. #5365-5373. Aired: 05/11/94-05/23/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 679)
  - Prod. #5374-5380. Aired: 05/24/94-06/01/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 680)
  - Prod. #5310-5317. Aired: 02/18/94-03/03/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 681)
  - Prod. #5318-5325. Aired: 03/03/94-03/15/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 682)
  - Prod. #5327-5333. Aired: 03/16/94-03/28/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 683)
  - Prod. #5334. Aired: 03/29/94. Notes: SCRIPT AND OUTLINE. (Box 684)
  - Prod. #5422-5424. Aired: 08/01/94-08/05/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 684)
  - Prod. #5425-5426. Aired: TBA. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 684)
  - Prod. #5427-5430. Aired: TBA. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 685)
  - Prod. #5431-5433. Aired: 08/22/94-08/24/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 685)
  - Prod. #5434-5439. Aired: 08/25/94-09/01/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 686)
  - Prod. #5440-5443. Aired: TBA. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 687)
  - Prod. #5513-5521. Aired: 12/20/94-12/30/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 688)
  - Prod. #5522-5528. Aired: 01/03/95-01/11/95. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 689)
  - Prod. #5529-5536. Aired: 01/12/95-01/23/95. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 690)
  - Prod. #5489-5496. Aired: 11/15/94-11/25/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 691)
  - Prod. #5497-5503. Aired: 11/28/94-12/06/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 692)
  - Prod. #5504-5512. Aired: 12/07/94-12/19/94. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 693)
  - Prod. #5536-5543. Aired: 01/23/95-02/01/95. Notes: SCRIPTS, REVISIONS, AND OUTLINES. (Box 694)
  - Prod. #5544-5550. Aired: 02/02/95-02/10/95. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 695)
  - Prod. #5551-5556. Aired: 02/13/95-2/20/95. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 696)
  - Prod. #5557-5562. Aired: 02/21/95-02/28/95. Notes: SCRIPTS, PRODUCTION BREAKDOWNS AND OUTLINES. (Box 697)
  - Prod. #5563-5568. Aired: 03/01/95-03/09/95. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 698)
  - Prod. #5569-5576. Aired: 03/13/95-03/24/95. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 699)
  - Prod. #5577-5581. Aired: 03/27/95-03/31/95. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 700)
  - Prod. #5590-5597. Aired: 04/13/95-04/24/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 701)
  - Prod. #5598-5604. Aired: 04/25/95-05/03/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 702)
  - Prod. #5605-5611. Aired: 05/04/95-05/12/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 703)
  - Prod. #5612-5618. Aired: 05/15/95-05/23/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 704)
  - Prod. #5619-5625. Aired: 05/24/95-06/02/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 705)
  - Prod. #5626-5628. Aired: 06/05/95-06/07/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 706)
  - Prod. #5582-5589. Aired: 04/03/95-04/12/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 707)
  - Prod. #5629-5636. Aired: 06/08/95-06/19/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 708)
  - Prod. #5637-5644. Aired: 06/20/95-06/29/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 709)
  - Prod. #5645-5651. Aired: 06/30/95-07/10/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 710)
  - Prod. #5652-5658. Aired: 07/11/95-07/19/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 711)
  - Prod. #5659-5665. Aired: 07/20/95-07/28/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 712)
  - Prod. #5666-5672. Aired: 07/31/95-08/08/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 713)
  - Prod. #5673-5679. Aired: 08/09/95-08/17/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 714)
  - Prod. #5680-5686. Aired: 08/18/95-08/28/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 715)
  - Prod. #5687-5694. Aired: 08/29/95-09/11/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 716)
  - Prod. #5695-5696. Aired: 09/12/95-09/13/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 717)
  - Prod. #5697-5703. Aired: 09/14/95-09/22/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 718)
  - Prod. #5704-5711. Aired: 09/25/95-10/04/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 719)
  - Prod. #5712-5718. Aired: 10/05/95-10/13/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 720)
  - Prod. #5719-5725. Aired: 10/16/95-10/24/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 721)
  - Prod. #5726-5732. Aired: 10/25/95-11/01/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 722)
  - Prod. #5733-5738. Aired: 11/02/95-11/09/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 723)
  - Prod. #5739-5745. Aired: 11/10/95-11/20/95. (Box 737)